It was quite warm today.
今日はだいぶ暖かかったね
It's warm today, isn't it?
暖かいですね、今日
I think I'm a little nervous today,
今日ちょっと緊張すると思うんだけど、
Well, your sister is coming.
あの、お姉さん来るから
I understand.
分かります
You're shy, aren't you?
人見知りだよね
get nervous.
緊張する
Because we're together.
一緒にいるから
She's an older sister, but isn't she cute?
お姉さんだけど可愛いでしょ?
It's cute.
可愛いです
Because it's small.
ちっちゃいから
Are you disturbing the announcer?
アナウンサー乱してます?
It's a little disorganized.
一応乱してます
She's messing with idols.
彼女はアイドル乱してます
That's right.
そうなんですね
Idol is disturbed.
アイドル乱してます
Isn't it cute?
可愛いでしょ?
My sister is also in love with idols.
お姉さんもアイドル恋ですよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Is there somewhere you want to go?
行きたいとこある?
Asakusa.
浅草
I don't come here often.
あんまり来ない
It's like an amusement park, a small amusement park.
なんか遊園地、ちっちゃい遊園地
Have you never been there?
行ったことないですか?
do not have.
ない
Well then, I guess I'll take you there.
じゃあ、連れてあげようかな
Yay!
やったー
So, should I go with Mullican?
じゃあ、マリカンで行きますか
Mullican?
マリカン?
Let's go.
行きましょう
The two of us haven't talked at all since a while ago,
さっきから2人全然喋らないけど、
Are you nervous?
緊張してるんでしょ?
It's a bit of a show off, isn't it?
ちょっと人見せりなんですよね
Right?
でしょ?
This child is done too.
この子も済みしいだからさ
That's why I can't talk much.
だから余計喋れない
Somehow, I can't speak for myself unless someone talks to me.
なんか、喋ってくれないと自分から話せない
So, if I keep quiet, I guess I'll just stay silent.
じゃあ、こっちが黙ってたら、黙ったまま過ごすみたいな
Remain silent.
黙ったまま
Isn't that painful?
それ辛くない?
I don't really mind the silence.
沈黙はそんなに気にならないんですよね
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's the same type.
同じタイプだ
I don't mind the silence.
沈黙気にならないよね
I'll be silent for the rest of my life.
一生沈黙になっちゃう
Wouldn't it be great if the two of us became idols?
2人でアイドルになったらいいんじゃないの?
Two people?
2人で?
Combi-kun.
コンビ君
But I really like idols.
でもアイドルすごい好きです
Oh, really?
あ、本当?
Should I change it?
変更したらいいのかな?
変更しようかな
Is it okay for the two of us to laugh?
2人で笑いでいいのかな?
Comedy?
お笑い?
We became friends like idols.
全然アイドルみたいに仲良くなっちゃった
Is there a comedy element?
お笑い要素あるかな?
A new genre that makes fun of idols.
アイドルにお笑いをかけて、新しいジャンル
Can you smile?
お 笑 い でき るかな?
It seems possible though.
できそうだけどな
Do you think you can do it?
できそうですか?
Can't you just say tsukkomi?
ツッコミとかできないかな?
Tsukkomi seems stupid.
ツッコミなんかボケっぽいよね
Like a tsukkomi.
ツッコミみたいな
Stay calm.
冷静に
interesting.
面白い
Isn't this good?
これ、いいんじゃない?
this?
これ?
cute.
かわいい
The bond between the two.
2人の絆
Do you want to wear them together?
お揃いで付ける?
It might be good.
いいかも
It has a ribbon.
リボン付いてる
Which one is better?
どっちがいいの?
Is this because she's an idol?
アイドルだからこっちかな?
It's different.
違うんだ
Like a boy.
男の子みたいな
Matching.
お揃い
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Tsukkomi?
ツッコミ?
It's cute.
かわいいね
かわいいじゃん
cute.
か わいい
かわいい
They match.
お揃いだ
Yay!
やったー
cute.
かわいい
I fell down a bit.
ちょっと落ちたよ
picture?
え?
Didn't you get it?
取れたんじゃない?
Did you get it?
取れちゃったの?
How did you get it?
どうやって取れたんだろう?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
On the head with strings attached.
ひも付いてる頭に
That doesn't exist anymore.
それがもうない
disappointing.
残念
What should I do?
どうしよう
Hold it cutely.
可愛く持って
Let me put it here.
ここに入れてあげて
Ah, good.
あ、いい
cute.
かわいい
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
With my partner.
相棒で
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
cute.
かわいい
Yay!
や ったー
Wow, this is what it feels like.
すごい、こんな感じなんだ
It was my first time here.
初めて来た
cute.
かわいい
I would also like to ask Yui-chan.
ゆいちゃんにも聞きたいと思う
This kid also wants to drink something.
この子も何か飲みたいんだよな
This is good.
これがいいって
Okay.
いいよ
oh,
お ー、
amazing.
すごい
Did it come out?
出 たかな?
It came out.
出た
Do you want something to drink?
何か飲みたいのある?
What is it?
何だろう?
Isn't this good?
これとかはいいんじゃない?
What is this?
何これ?
The one that spins around.
くるくるって回るやつ
Is it scary?
怖いかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Shall we go?
行ってみようか
That's amazing, I guess.
すごいね、やっぱ
That's amazing.
すごいわ
It was amazing.
すごかった
Was it amazing?
すごかった?
Okay.
よっしゃー
I'm going.
行ってきます
Is it scary?
怖いかな?
I'm going.
行 ってきます
It's impossible to be scared.
怖いのが無理ですね
It's scary.
怖 いの
Do your best and turn it around.
頑張って回せ
It's so scary.
めっちゃ怖い
While the vehicle is moving, hold onto the safety belt in front of you with both hands.
乗り物が動いている間は、前の安全帯に両手でしっかりと つかま
Please say that.
って いってください
I'm going.
行ってきます
I was surprised.
びっくりした
I found some pandas.
なんかパンタ見つけた
Panta?
パ ンタ?
It's so shiny.
すごい光ってる
It's shining though.
光 ってるんだけど
Is it shining?
光ってる?
difficult.
難しい
Everyone is watching.
みんな見てる
I really want to do it.
めっちゃやりたい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Also.
また
See you again.
また、またにして
That's amazing.
すごいね
The momentum is amazing.
勢いがすごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
That's enough, that's enough.
もういいですよ、それ
All you have to do is light a fire here.
ここにさ、お火についてあればいいんだよ
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Is that not stable?
それがさ、安定しない?
difficult.
難しい
Did you get it right?
当たった?
It's not a hit.
当たってない
Not at all.
全然当たってない
Not right?
当たってない?
It looks great on you.
すごい似合ってる
It suits you so well.
めっちゃ似合ってる
Not at all.
全然当たんない
Do you want to rekan?
リカンする?
I want to play Prikan.
プリカンやりたい
Take a picture of the two of you with Ninjan.
2人、ニンジャン一緒に撮って
I'm fine, I want to take a picture.
元気ね、撮りたい
amazing.
すごい
The feeling of diving is terrible.
潜水感ひどい
潜水感やばい
5 people, 10 people.
5人、10人
10、9、 10、11、 7、6、
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, It's over soon.
5、4、 3、2、 1、 先々終了
I thought you might entertain me,
ボクを楽しませてもらおうかなと思って、
for now.
とりあえず
Are you ready for this?
この準備はいいですか?
Can we both become MZs?
2人で MZなってもらっていい?
There are so many things I want to see.
観賞したいな、いろいろ
Want to watch it?
観賞したい?
Please open your legs.
足開いてください
For two people.
2人で
Ah, it was store-bought bread after all.
あ、やっぱりそれ店パンだったんだね
It's black.
黒いの
I was outside a little bit, and I said, ``Black, black.''
外でちょっとね、黒、黒だって言ってたら、
I was talking about this.
これのこと言ってたんだけど
Is that so?
そういうこと?
Yes, I was deceived.
そう、騙された
I see.
なるほど
I was deceived.
騙されちゃったよ
You're wearing something white.
白っぽいの着てるよね
Oh, can you see that too?
あ、それも見える?
I can see it now.
今見えてる
picture?
え?
What color are you wearing those pants?
それ何色着てパンツ履いてるの?
It's greenish.
緑っぽい
The green one?
緑っぽいやつ?
Fresh green effect.
新緑効果
Seeking healing.
癒しを求めて
Which one comes first?
どっちが最初?
You'll be confused if you include two people.
迷っちゃうよね、2人入れたらね
Look, look.
見て、見て
picture?
え?
why?
なんで?
Look, look.
見て、見て
Let's watch it together.
一緒に見よう
It's sticking out.
はみ出てる
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's sticking out.
はみ出てるよ
I like it, how perfect it is.
いいね、このミッチリ具合
I like this.
これ好き
He's so good that it's a waste to be an announcer.
アナウンサーにしてもったいないくらいスペスペだね、
feet.
足
Supese?
スペスペ?
I wish I could find a time to make use of this special skill.
このスペスペを生かした時ごと探したらいいのに
Is there such a thing?
そんなのある?
Something sexy.
セクシー系とか
Sexy?
セクシー系?
It's going to be a lot different.
だいぶ違くなっちゃう
White?
白色?
Are you looking at it?
ちょっと見てる?
Take a look.
ちょっと覗いてみて
why?
なんで?
Take a look.
覗いてみて
If you were an older sister, you would wear something like this.
お姉さんだったらこういうの履くんだよ、
As for the pants.
パンツは
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's stopped.
止められてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Since it's a shop panty, I'd like you to take off just the bottom.
それで店パンだから、下だけ脱いでもらおうかな
I think she would be happier if you wore pants.
パンツになってもらった方が彼女も喜ぶと思うから
Would you like it?
喜びますかね
Yeah, I think you'll probably like it.
うん、多分喜ぶと思う
Do you know?
知るですか?
I want to see your sister's pussy.
お姉さんのマンコ見たいよね
Can I sit here and take a look?
ここに座って覗いてもいい?
If I sit there, can I just lie down?
そこに座ったら、横たまりでいい?
Her skin color is authentic.
オーベンチックだね、肌の色は
beautiful.
綺麗
Isn't it yellow?
黄色くない?
Like the Japanese.
日本人みたいに
white.
白い
Beautiful skin, be it red, white or blue.
赤白いってか、青いってか、綺麗な肌
Eh, you're not half-Japanese or anything, right?
え、ハーフとかじゃないですよね?
It's not.
じゃないです
Your skin is beautiful.
肌綺麗ですね
I like this, this kind of pose.
これ好きなんですよ、こういうポーズのこれが
Is this a hindrance?
これが邪魔かな?
This is a hindrance.
これが邪魔ですね
Look at it like this.
こうやって覗いて
It's embarrassing to even look at it.
見てるのも恥ずかしいって
It's so embarrassing.
とっても恥ずかしい
If I sit here, will I react somehow?
ここ座ったら、なんか反応するのかな?
I want to see your sister's reaction.
お姉さんの反応するとか見てみたい
I guess this is a bit of a reaction.
ちょっと反応するかな、これ
Eh, come around here, around here.
え、この辺、この辺来て
Will it not react?
反応しないのかな?
I did, look.
したよ、ほら
I'm doing it.
してるしてる
Soft and squishy.
柔らかーい、ぷにぷに
It's squishy.
ぷにぷにしてる
Huh, it's squishy, ​​isn't it?
え、ぷにぷにしてるよね?
Give me a little help.
ちょっと手をかして
Just point me.
ちょっと指かして
Touch it and make it squishy.
触ってみて、ぷにぷにして
copper?
どう?
Puni Puni?
ぷにぷに?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
恥ずかしいのか
Wouldn't it be lonely if we were just together?
一緒にだけだと寂しいでしょ?
You don't think you're the only one who won't come, right?
自分だけ来ないと思ってないでしょ?
Just open this up.
ちょっとこれ開いて
This is cloth.
布じゃん、これ
It's cloth, isn't it?
布だよね
cloth pants.
布パンツ
Aren't they cloth pants?
布パンツじゃない?
this.
これ
different?
違う?
Like 100% main.
メイン100%みたいな
Is it different?
違うのかな?
I don't know.
分かんない
It seems like that.
それっぽいみたいなんだけど
It's stained.
シミになってる
Wait a minute, this.
ちょっと、これ
Really?
本当に?
Will it feel good if I touch you someday?
いつか触ったら気持ちよくなっちゃう?
Is that what you mean?
そういうことなんですか?
Does this happen when you touch it?
触ったらこうした?
Is that what you mean?
そう いうこと?
terrible.
やばい
Don't you like girls?
女の子好きなんじゃないの?
Maybe.
もしかして
The cloth pants look big.
布パンツ大きそうだね
It's not big.
大きくない
Isn't it big?
大きくないの?
It's not big.
大きくないです
I look at her with hatred.
恨ましそうに見てるけど
Are you there?
いる?
Okay, I'll give you a place to lower it.
いいよ、下げるところあげる
I'll give you a place to lower it.
下 げるところあげる
Yes, everything.
そうだね、全部
oh
お
Pai.
っぱ い
Shall I touch it first?
先触っちゃおうかな
It's big.
大きいじゃん
大きいよ
This is big.
大きいじゃん、これ
About D cup.
Dカップくらい
If you look at the back of the plastic, isn't it written there?
プラの後ろ見たら書いてあるんじゃない?
Wash too much.
洗いすぎて
It's D.
Dだ
Look, it's D.
ほら、Dだ
It's pink.
ピンクじゃん
ピ ンクだ
It probably feels the same, I'm sure.
もっとも同じ感じなんでしょう、きっと
It's pink.
ピンク色なんだ
Try touching it.
触ってみてよ
Try touching it, little one.
触ってみてよ、チクビ
My breasts are soft, so try touching them.
おっぱい柔らかいから触ってみてよ
Give me a hand.
手出して
It's soft, squishy.
柔らかいよ、プニプニ
It's so squishy.
プニプニだね
Maybe I should touch you here.
ここ触ってあげたらよいかも
Touch, touch.
触って、触って
Let's touch it together.
触るから一緒に
Touched by two people.
2人に触られて
Try to touch it so that it feels good when you are touched.
自分が触られたら気持ちいいように触ってみて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I guess you like software?
ソフトが好きなんだったっけ?
soft.
ソフト
Do you like software?
ソフト好き?
Do you like Hallowalt?
ハロウォルトが好き?
Which one?
どっち?
Which one do you like?
どっちが好き?
Do you like cutlets?
カツリが好きなのか?
soft?
ソフト?
Over there.
そっち
You can lick me there.
そっち、こっち舐めていいよ
Lick this.
こっち舐めて
Lick it, lick it.
舐めて、舐めて
That part is good.
その辺、いい
Lick me more.
もっと舐めて
Lick it more.
も っと舐めて
Isn't it wet?
ぬれてんじゃないの?
Isn't it wet here?
こっちぬれてんじゃないの?
I'm sure you'll get it, first.
きっと掴めてよ、先
It's wet and wet.
ぬれてる、びっちゃびちゃ
It's so wet.
すごいびちゃびちゃ
Oh no, this is it.
やば、これ
Ya ba.
や ば
Let's take a look at your butt too.
お尻も見てみようか
Look behind you.
後ろ見て
My sister's panties.
お姉さんのパンティ
Try sticking it out a little.
ちょっと突き出してみて
Look.
ほ ら
It's your sister's butt.
お姉さんのお尻だよ
Sounds good, right?
いい音するでしょ?
It sounds good.
いい音する
Look.
ほ ら
Just passing by.
すれすれ
Butt diagonal, together.
お尻斜めよ、一緒に
No way.
やだ
So, can I take it off?
じゃあ、脱がしていい?
Everything already.
もう全部
Can I take it off?
脱がしていいの?
Wow, I saw it.
うわー、見ちゃった
I haven't seen it.
見てない
見てないよ
Spread it out.
広げて
It's so wet.
めっちゃぬれてる
You've never seen me wet, have you?
ぬれてるの見たことないでしょ?
You can't tell that you're wet, right?
自分でぬれてるの分かんないでしょ?
Look, it's shining, so here it is.
見て、光ってるから、ここ
It's shining.
光ってるね
My pants are dirty.
パンツ汚れてるもんだって
パ ンツ汚れてる
Oh no, I won't be able to go home if I don't dry it.
やばい、乾かさないと帰れなくなっちゃう
Is he the only one with skin?
一人だけ肌か
Only one person.
一人だけ
Only one person had skin, so I took a picture of this.
一人だけ肌か、これを撮っちゃって
You look like a model drawing.
デッサンしてる、モデルさんみたいだよね
drawing model.
デッサンモデル
Look here.
こっち見て
Look at your body.
体こっち見て
Will you become an MG and become a drawing model?
MGになってデッサンモデルになってくれる?
I want to see her.
彼女見たいんだって
Why that much?
なんでそれだけ?
In order, in order.
順番、順番
Open your legs.
足開いて
Open more.
もっと開いて
Look.
見て
It's a drawing model.
デッサンモデルだわ
Where do you want to see?
どこ見たい?
I want to see it here.
ここ 見たい
in trouble?
困る?
Don't watch Cough or anything.
コフとか見てんじゃんよ
He's someone I've never compared to.
比べたことない人だぜ
Others have never seen it before.
他の人も見たことない人
Every girl has different skin.
女の子、一人一人、肌違うんだよ
Do you understand?
分かるんですか?
I understand.
分かる
And now, we are divided by comparison.
しかも今、比べて分かれちゃう
Yes, let's compare.
そう、比べてみよう
there were.
あった
Beautiful pussy.
綺麗なおまんこ
It's pink, after all.
ピンクだね、やっぱ
I'll spread it out.
広げるよ
I'm watching it seriously.
真剣に見てるよ
I'm looking very seriously.
超 真剣に見てる
What were you thinking?
何に考えてたの?
It's my first time seeing it.
初めて見るけど
You should take a closer look.
もっと近くで見ていいよ
Look closer.
近くで見て
Look.
ほ ら
Isn't it beautiful?
綺麗でしょ?
I guess I'll lick it, then.
舐めちゃおうかな、じゃあ
Sit a little deeper.
ちょっと浅めに座って
Can you sit here and watch?
こっち座って見てくれない?
You want me to see it, right?
見てほしいよね?
No way.
いやー
Look at the face you're about to make.
出しそうな顔見て
It's a really beautiful body.
めっちゃ綺麗な体だね
Let's pull together for a moment, here.
ちょっと一緒に引いてみようよ、こっち
Why?
何で?
Stand up, stand up.
立って立って
Stand up for a moment.
ちょっと立って
Show me your body.
見せて体
beautiful.
綺麗
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
Very stylish.
めっちゃスタイルいい
Look.
ほ ら
This time it's this way.
今度こっちだよ
I'll come.
来るよ
Can you just look at my waistcoat?
チョッキだけ見てくれない?
Waistcoat?
チョッキ?
It's getting dry.
乾かくなってる
Because you touched me earlier.
さっき触られたから
Is it possible to touch yourself?
自力に触るのってある?
Is that so?
そうなの?
I feel sorry.
申し訳ない気がする
Then you'll be touched more.
じゃあ、もっと触られちゃうよ
vice versa.
逆に
I'll go there.
そっち行くで
Why don't you go?
行 っていかない?
Wanty and this is important.
ワンティとこれ大事なのがね
Did you go here?
こ っち行った?
I was going this way though.
こっち行ってたけどね
Feet, feet.
足、足
feet.
足
A little foot, foot.
ちょっと足、足
My legs were wrapped around me.
足を巻かれかかって
Open your legs.
足開いて
You took your clothes off, anyway.
脱いでんでしょ、どうせ
Look, look.
ほら、見て
Because the stains are terrible.
しみがすごいから
It's true.
本当だ
I'm hiding it.
隠してる
Show me, show me.
見せて、見せて
The stains are terrible.
しみがすごい
There are also new stains.
新しいしみも出てるよ
I was able to do this distance.
この距離できてた
Look, I've removed this.
これほら、抜いてる
Did you show it like this?
こう見せたの?
Did you lick her boobs and show her like this?
おっぱい舐めて、こう見せたの?
Like Buddha.
仏様みたいな
It's like there's a Buddha.
仏様がいるみたいな
I'm afraid, but I'd like to touch on it.
恐れ多いけど、触らせていただきます
Are you taking pictures here?
こ っち撮ってるかな?
Just touching.
触ってるだけ
It's awkward, isn't it?
気まずいよね
Wouldn't it be better if you just touched her since it would be awkward?
気まずいから触ってあげたほうがいいんじゃない?
It's awkward just being there, isn't it?
ただいるだけって気まずいでしょ
Let me touch you a little.
ちょっと触ってあげて
It's fun to take pictures of this.
これ撮ってたら楽しいから
Even if I was just taking a picture of this.
これ 撮ってただけでも
Touch me like you always do with women.
自分がいつも女にしてるみたいに触ってあげてよ
When Tachi always pretends to be a woman.
たちさんのいつも女にしてる時は
How did you touch it?
どうやって触ってあげたの?
It should feel like you're touching your own pussy.
自分のおまん子を触っている感覚になればいいんだね
difficult.
難しい
Go back a little bit.
ちょっと後ろに回り込んでよ
Get behind her.
彼女の後ろに回り込んで
Put it in here like this and spread your legs.
こう やってここに入れて、足開いて
Open your legs?
足開いて?
yes.
そう
This is also very difficult, so I opened it like this.
これも大変あって、こう開いて
It's at an angle that makes it look like you're touching it yourself.
自分で触っているような角度になるじゃん
My hands.
手が
yes.
そう
It hasn't reached the air conditioning room.
空調室まで届いてない
I don't know where else.
もうどこか分からない
Just a little more.
もうちょっとした
Around there.
そこらへん
It looks really good.
すごいよく見える
From here.
こっちから
Looks like it's wet.
濡れてるような
I was always touching it.
いつ も 触ってたんだ
That's what it feels like.
そんな感じなんだ
everytime.
いつも
It looks like Aridas.
アリダスって見えるんだけど
I see Aridas.
アリダスが見える
It's a sports bra.
スポブラだ
You're wearing a sports bra.
スポブラ履いてるんだね
amazing.
すごい
These are also sports pants.
これもスポパンツ
Is that so?
そういうこと?
It's Aridas.
アリダスじゃん
Fashionable.
おしゃれ
I want to see your boobs.
おっぱい見たいよね
What kind of chikubi?
どんなチクビか
I don't like it.
嫌だ
My hands are cold.
手冷たい
That's good.
いいよね
My hands are cold.
手冷たい
Don't you always pull it without permission?
いつ も勝手に引っ張らない?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Did it hurt?
痛ったの?
You have a clean face.
すっきりした顔してる
It's refreshing, isn't it?
すっきりしてるよね
This is how it happened.
こうしてきた
Very much.
すごく
Please make yourself both comfortable for a moment.
ちょっと二人で気持ちよくしてください
Two people.
二 人で
You look kind of happy.
なんか嬉しそうだね
Why don't you just sit with me for a day?
そのまま一日も一緒に座ってくんない?
For two people.
二人で
Like a lover.
恋人みたいな
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
Drink your dick together.
一緒におちんちん飲みて
Can we drink dick together?
一緒におちんちん飲めれる?
Don't spread it.
広げないでよ
It's very narrow.
すごい狭い
My niece.
めいきだ
Her body is clean and her insides are clean too.
体もきれいだし中もきれいだ
Will you let me drink your sister's breasts too?
お姉さんのおっぱいも飲めてあげてくれる?
older sister
お 姉 さん
Can you drink my breasts too?
の おっぱいも飲んであげてくれる?
It looks like it's getting wet.
びちゃびちゃいそうです
I'm sweating a lot.
すんごい汗かけてる
This one also has a lot of toshi.
こっちもトシの量が多い
Sit over here with your right hand.
右手でこっち座って
over there.
あそこ
I can see it.
見えちゃうよ
It looks like a baby is being born.
赤 ちゃん生まれてきてるみたい
You can make a face.
顔ができるよ
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
Do you feel like you don't know?
知らない気分?
Selfish?
儘々しい?
It's so selfish.
儘々しいよね
Hit the back
奥に当たる
Yo.
よ
Do you want to taste your sister's manjuli?
お 姉さんのマンジュリの味する?
Okay.
いいよ
Is it okay if I cum inside you?
中出してもいいの?
Okay.
いいよ
Try letting it out.
ひだまく出してみて
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You look like someone who has been raped.
犯された人みたいになってるよ
Can you see it?
見えるかな?
Look at your hands?
手のところ見る?
This is staying.
これとどまってる
Can we hold a cleaning fair?
お掃除フェアとかできる?
Can you throw it?
投げてくれる?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I want to put it out here too.
こっちにも出したいな
Do you sit and grow?
座って大きくなるの?
Maybe it's getting bigger?
もしかして大きくなってる?
Is it happening?
なってる?
a little bit?
ちょっと?
We saw each other.
見え合った
Show me how you feel.
感じてる顔見せてあげて
You can see that.
あれ見えだね
Try touching my dick and pussy.
ちんことまんこ触ってみて
Chest and chair.
くりといすと
Turn it.
手回して
Turn it now.
これから回して
From where?
どっから?
I want you to sleep here.
ここに寝てほしい
My hands are getting stained again.
また手染まってきちゃった
terrible.
やばい
please.
お願いします
I have a neck so can you lick it with me again?
ネックルがあるからまた一緒に舐めてくれる?
Do you like felt?
フェルト好き?
I'm starting to feel like I'm about to release something.
なんか出そうになってきちゃった
Yo.
よ
Odor Yes.
臭 そうだ
It doesn't smell.
臭くないよ
I wanted to see them love each other.
二人が愛し合ってるところ見たいと思って
Where we love each other?
愛し合ってるところ?
It looks like Earth.
地球みたいだね
surely.
確かに
Try running it in the sink.
流ししてみて下
Ah, this.
あ、これ
amazing.
すごい
It's quite tiring.
結構しんどくしい
amazing.
すごい
At first it was g.
最初はグ
It's like rock, paper, scissors.
じゃんけんぽい
It's Aiko, right?
あいこでしょ
So which one is better?
じゃあ先どっちがいい?
Slow silo.
スローサイロー
Then please lower it.
じゃあ下げてください
amazing.
すごい
I think of sparkling eyes.
目キラキラって考えてる
Then open your legs.
じゃあ足開いてみて
Open your legs.
足開いて
It's like a medical examination.
診察みたいな感じで
My body feels really bad.
自分の体がすごいしんどい
I get itchy.
かゆくなっちゃう
Let me look at you.
見つめてあげて
Look at the face that makes you feel.
感じてる顔見つめてあげて
My face got cut.
顔切れちゃった
Go a little further down.
もうちょっと下に行って
I was able to stretch out my pants.
パンツ伸ばしてあげてもらえた
Sorry if I made you stretch.
伸ばしてもらったらごめんなさい
Are you stretching it?
伸ばしてるの?
It feels good.
気持ちよさそう
air
気
Looks like it will last a long time.
持 ちよさそう
It looks really comfortable.
め っちゃ気持ちよさそうだね
Is it here?
ここかな?
ここですか?
Is the amount of force okay?
力加減大丈夫ですか?
Make it stronger?
もっと強くする?
I'll make it even stronger.
も っと強くします
I think it's easier to make it stronger.
強くしやすいんだと思うよ
Is that so?
そういうこと?
I feel like that.
そうな気がする
Never go to this.
絶対行くな、これ
I'll probably go now.
今多分行くよ
Please give me something in return.
お返ししてあげて
The itching is because the opener is coming out.
かゆきはオーパーが出てるからね
It's not like we're going to do it on paper.
オ ーパーペーペーで行くわけじゃない
This is cute.
これがかわいい
It's dejax.
デジャックスだよね
You want to feel good, right?
気持ちよく行きたいでしょ
I want you to go comfortably.
気持ちよく行ってほしいな
Relax.
リラックスして
relax?
リラックス?
Turn around to that side.
そっち側回って
I asked her to let me go.
彼女に行かせてくださいとお願いして
please.
お願いします
It's a big responsibility because I was asked to do it.
お願いされちゃったから責任重大だよ
Is it strong?
強いの?
Because I have added breasts.
おっぱい足してるから
Add some boobs to show off.
アピールしてるからおっぱい足して
A woman who makes an adult lick her breasts.
大人におっぱいを舐めさせる女
I'm sleeping right now.
すぐ寝てる
It's so wet.
びちゃびちゃじゃん
I'm sleeping.
寝てるよ
Say you're going.
行っちゃうって言って
What are you two doing?
二人で何やってるんですか?
What are you doing?
何してるんだろう
Did you feel refreshed?
スッキリしましたか?
yes.
はい
It felt refreshing.
スッキリした
Understood.
分かったね
This is also refreshing.
こっちもスッキリしました
Take it out a third time.
3回目出して
Good luck to both of you in the future.
じゃあ二人とも頑張ってね、将来
I will do my best.
頑張ります
I'll help you as much as possible.
なるべくちょうど助けるからね
Are you two saying goodbye?
二人バイバイしてんの?
I don't know.
分かんない